A Guide to the Berryman United Methodist Church (Richmond, Va.) Records, 1913-2003
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Berryman United Methodist Church (Richmond, Va.) Records, 1913-2003
The Library of Virginia
43173
25.25 cubic feet (56 boxes)
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Gift of John Kirn, Midlothian.
Historical Information
Berryman United Methodist Church was organized in Richmond, Virginia on 5 October 1913 at the home of Rev. Albert C. Berryman. It was originally known as Woodland Heights Methodist Episcopal Church, South, and there were 34 members. The group met in a small wood frame structure until 1925, when a new building was constructed. Two years later, the name of the church was changed to Berryman Methodist Episcopal, in memory of the church's first pastor. There were two more name changes - in 1939, to Berryman Methodist Church, and in 1968, to Berryman United Methodist Church. A new educational building was constructed in 1938. In 2003, the church membership voted to merge with Mt. Pisgah United Methodist Church in Midlothian, Virginia, and Berryman ceased to exist.
Scope and Content
Records, 1913-2003, of Berryman United Methodist Church in Richmond, Virginia. Includes bulletins, charge conference materials, correspondence, membership rolls and transfers, minutes, newsletters, photographs, programs, reports, scrapbooks, Sunday school class rolls and record books, and yearbooks. There are also financial records, including account books, bank statements, budgets, check registers, contributions, invoices, ledgers, investment information, receipts, and treasurer's reports.
Contents List
- Addressograph Multigraph Corporation. (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Administrative Board, 1971-1976. (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Administrative Board, 1991-1997. (Box 1, Folder 3)
- All Saints Day. (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Anniversary Programs. (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Annual Conference Reports, 1978-1994. (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Annual Conference Reports, 1995-2001. (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Autism Center - VCU. (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Baptism Certificates, 5 April 1953 - 3 April 1955. (Box 1, Folder 9)
- "Berryman Beacon," 1951-1955. (Box 1, Folder 10-13)
- "Berryman Beacon," 1956-1964. (Box 2, Folder 1-9)
- "Berryman Beacon," 1965-1966, 1973-1989. (Box 3, Folder 1-19)
- "Berryman Beacon," 1990-1991, 1993, 1995-2003. (Box 4, Folder 1-12)
- "Berryman Beacon" Material, 1969-1970. (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Budget, 1975-1980. (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Budget, 1981-1994. (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Budget, 1995-1997. (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Budget, 1998-2003. (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Birthdays of Berryman Church, 1974-2001. (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Building Maintenance. (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Bulletins, 1 June 1955 - 30 May 1956. (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Bulletins, June 1956 - May 1964. (Box 5, Folder 1-9)
- Bulletins, June 1964 - December 1973. (Box 6, Folder 1-10)
- Bulletins, 1974-1979. (Box 7, Folder 1-6)
- Bulletins, 1980-1986. (Box 8, Folder 1-8)
- Bulletins, 1987-1994. (Box 9, Folder 1-8)
- Bulletins, 1995-2001. (Box 10, Folder 1-7)
- Bulletins, 2002-2003. (Box 11, Folder 1-2)
- Bulletins (Christmas). (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Bulletins (Special). (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Burglar Alarm. (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Burial Records, 1967-1969. (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Calendars. (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Cambodian Relief. (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Census. (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Central Fidelity. (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Certificate of Assignment, 1919. (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Certificates of Transfer, 1964-1966. (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Charge Conferences, 1976-1980. (Box 11, Folder 13-17)
- Charge Conferences, 1981-1994. (Box 12, Folder 1-14)
- Charge Conferences, 1995-2003. (Box 13, Folder 1-9)
- Charter Members - Woman's Society of Christian Service, 1940. (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Check Registers, 1998, 2001. (Box 14, Folder 2-5)
- Chestnut Hill Methodist Church (Lynchburg). (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Children's Choir. (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Children's Festival, 1997. (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Children's Festival Evaluations, 1996. (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Chrismon. (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Church School Rolls, 1974-1984. (Box 14, Folder 11)
- Class Rolls, 1959-1961. (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Class Rolls - Adult Division, 1965-1966. (Box 14, Folder 13)
- Class Rolls - Children's Division, 1965-1966. (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Class Rolls - Youth Division, 1965-1966. (Box 14, Folder 15)
- Cokesbury Envelope Service. (Box 14, Folder 16)
- Committee on Ministerial Scholarship, 1959-1960. (Box 14, Folder 17)
- Committees. (Box 14, Folder 18)
- Communicant and Membership. (Box 14, Folder 19)
- Confirmation Letters. (Box 14, Folder 20)
- Contributions, 1988-1990. (Box 15, Folder 1-6)
- Contributions, 1990-1992. (Box 16, Folder 1-6)
- Contributions, 1992, 1994-1996. (Box 17, Folder 1-5)
- Contributions, 1996-1999. (Box 18, Folder 1-7)
- Contributions, 1999-2002. (Box 19, Folder 1-8)
- Contributions, 2003. (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Correspondence, 1956-1968. (Box 20, Folder 2-4)
- Correspondence, June 1977 - March 1981. (Box 20, Folder 5)
- Correspondence (Miscellaneous), 1977-1981. (Box 20, Folder 6)
- Correspondence, 1981-1984. (Box 20, Folder 7)
- Correspondence, 1985-1987. (Box 20, Folder 8)
- Correspondence, 1988. (Box 20, Folder 9)
- Correspondence, 1989. (Box 20, Folder 10)
- Correspondence, 1991. (Box 20, Folder 11)
- Correspondence, 1992. (Box 20, Folder 12)
- Correspondence, 1994. (Box 20, Folder 13)
- Correspondence, 1995-2003. (Box 21, Folder 1-7)
- Council on Ministries. (Box 21, Folder 8)
- Cradle Roll Certificate, 1926. (Box 21, Folder 9)
- Crestar. (Box 21, Folder 10)
- Davenport and Company, 1998-2001. (Box 21, Folder 11-14)
- Diary, 1961. (Box 21, Folder 15)
- "Dollars and Sense". (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Dorothy Owens Wesleyan Service Guild - Scrapbook, 1953-1956. (Box 56)
- Dorothy Owens Wesleyan Service Guild - Scrapbook, 1957-1959. (Box 56)
- Dorothy Owens Wesleyan Service Guild - Scrapbook, 1960-1983. (Box 56)
- Eagles, Doris - Estate. (Box 22, Folder 2)
- Equipment Manuals. (Box 22, Folder 3)
- Estimates of Support, 1980-1981. (Box 22, Folder 4)
- Event Planning. (Box 22, Folder 5)
- Final Worship Service, 22 June 2003. (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Finance Committee, 1977-1987. (Box 22, Folder 7)
- Finance Committee, 1988-2000. (Box 22, Folder 8)
- Financial Letters, 1975-1987. (Box 22, Folder 9)
- Financial Reports, 1989-1990, 1993-1994. (Box 22, Folder 10-13)
- Financial Reports, 1995-1998. (Box 23, Folder 1-6)
- Financial Reports, 1998-2001. (Box 24, Folder 1-5)
- Foodbank, 1994-1996. (Box 24, Folder 6)
- George Washington Banquet. (Box 24, Folder 7)
- Global Board of Missions. (Box 24, Folder 8)
- Grief. (Box 24, Folder 9)
- Habitat for Humanity. (Box 24, Folder 10)
- Healing Service. (Box 24, Folder 11)
- Homes for Aging. (Box 25, Folder 1-3)
- Hospice. (Box 25, Folder 4)
- Hymns and Songs. (Box 25, Folder 5)
- Hypes, Aldine - Living Will. (Box 25, Folder 6)
- Igniting Ministry. (Box 25, Folder 7)
- Intermediate Dept. - Secretary's Book, 1932-1933. (Box 25, Folder 8)
- Intermediate Dept. - Secretary's Book, 1933-1934. (Box 25, Folder 9)
- Intermediate Dept. - Treasurer's Book, 1932-1933. (Box 25, Folder 10)
- "The Interpreter". (Box 25, Folder 11)
- Invoices, 1980-1984. (Box 25, Folder 12-14)
- Invoices, 1994. (Box 25, Folder 15)
- Invoices, 1994. (Box 26, Folder 1-5)
- Invoices, 1995. (Box 26, Folder 6)
- Invoices, 1996. (Box 26, Folder 7-12)
- Invoices, 1997. (Box 27, Folder 1-5)
- Invoices, 1998. (Box 27, Folder 6-10)
- Invoices, 1998. (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Invoices, 1999. (Box 28, Folder 2)
- Invoices, 2000. (Box 28, Folder 3-8)
- Invoices, 2001. (Box 28, Folder 9-11)
- Invoices, 2001. (Box 29, Folder 1-3)
- Invoices, 2002. (Box 29, Folder 4-9)
- Joy Club. (Box 29, Folder 10)
- Kitchen Inventory. (Box 29, Folder 11)
- "Legislation for the Local Church". (Box 30, Folder 1)
- "Managing Your Church Assets". (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Manchester Lodge No. 14 - Bank Books, 1969-1999. (Box 30, Folder 3)
- Map of Berryman Church and Surrounding Neighborhoods, 2003. (Map-case 2, Drawer 13)
- M.A.R.C.H. (Metropolitan Area Resource Clearing House). (Box 30, Folder 4)
- Maundy Thursday Service. (Box 30, Folder 5)
- McDaniel, Edgar R. - Estate. (Box 30, Folder 6)
- Membership Certificate, 1980. (Box 30, Folder 7)
- Membership Directory, 1978. (Box 30, Folder 8)
- Membership Roll, 1939-1940. (Box 30, Folder 9)
- Membership Roll, 1966-1967. (Box 30, Folder 10)
- Membership Roll, 1964-1978. (Box 54)
- Membership Roll, 1964-2003. (Box 54)
- Membership Roll, 1988. (Box 30, Folder 11)
- Membership Transfers, 28 November 1943 - 11 November 1945. (Box 30, Folder 12)
- Membership Transfers, 1 December 1945 - 2 June 1947. (Box 30, Folder 13)
- Membership Transfers, 26 June 1947 - 5 October 1948. (Box 30, Folder 14)
- Membership Transfers, 27 October 1948 - 9 December 1949. (Box 30, Folder 15)
- Membership Transfers, 21 December 1949 - 12 March 1951. (Box 30, Folder 16)
- Membership Transfers, 19 March 1951 - 23 January 1953. (Box 30, Folder 17)
- Membership Transfers, 5 February 1953 - 28 March 1954. (Box 30, Folder 18)
- Membership Transfers, 30 March 1954 - 12 July 1955. (Box 30, Folder 19)
- Membership Transfers, 18 July 1955 - 25 January 1957. (Box 30, Folder 20)
- Membership Transfers, 29 January 1957 - 31 March 1958. (Box 30, Folder 21)
- Membership Transfers, 26 April 1958 - 25 June 1959. (Box 30, Folder 22)
- Membership Transfers, 10 August 1959 - 10 October 1960. (Box 30, Folder 23)
- Membership Transfers, 1 June 1962 - 30 May 1967. (Box 30, Folder 24)
- Membership Transfers, 1996-2003. (Box 31, Folder 1)
- Merger. (Box 31, Folder 2)
- Men's Bible Class, 1930-1940. (Box 31, Folder 3-6)
- Men's Bible Class - Banquet Information, Lists, Receipts, etc., 1974-1993. (Box 31, Folder 7)
- Men's Bible Class - Banquet Menus, 1974-1993. (Box 31, Folder 8)
- Men's Bible Class - Contributions to Building Fund, 1938-1944. (Box 31, Folder 9)
- Men's Bible Class - Roll Books, 1928-1963. (Box 49)
- Minutes - Administrative Board, 27 February 1977 - 11 July 1982. (Box 31, Folder 10)
- Minutes - Administrative Council, 23 January 1995 - 27 January 2003. (Box 31, Folder 11-12)
- Minutes - Administrative Council, 2002-2003. (Box 32, Folder 1)
- Minutes - Board of Stewards, 1931-1938. (Box 32, Folder 2-3)
- Minutes - Board of Stewards, 1934. (Box 32, Folder 4)
- Minutes - Board of Stewards, 26 September 1938 - 14 July 1940. (Box 32, Folder 5)
- Minutes - Board of Stewards, 8 July 1940 - 12 October 1942. (Box 32, Folder 6)
- Minutes - Board of Stewards, 28 October 1942 - 8 October 1945. (Box 32, Folder 7)
- Minutes - Board of Stewards, 22 October 1945 - 13 October 1952. (Box 32, Folder 8)
- Minutes - Board of Stewards, April 1965 - December 1967. (Box 32, Folder 9)
- Minutes - Board of Stewards, January 1968 - June 1969. (Box 32, Folder 10)
- Minutes - Circle 5, 7 January 1941 - 4 December 1944. (Box 32, Folder 11)
- Minutes - Circle 5, 4 December 1944 - 7 December 1948. (Box 33, Folder 1)
- Minutes - Dorothy Owens Guild, March 1953 - December 1961. (Box 33, Folder 2-3)
- Minutes - Finance Committee, 15 February 1976 - 10 September 1998. (Box 33, Folder 4-5)
- Minutes - Finance Committee, 26 March 1996 - 30 March 2003. (Box 33, Folder 6)
- Minutes - Gleaners Class, 14 October 1940 - 4 January 1943. (Box 33, Folder 7)
- Minutes - Ladies Bible Class, 1941-1949. (Box 33, Folder 8)
- Minutes - Ladies Bible Class, 31 January 1983 - 31 October 1988. (Box 33, Folder 9)
- Minutes - Men's Bible Class, 16 January 1941 - 15 June 1944, 1950. (Box 33, Folder 10)
- Minutes - Missionary Auxiliary, 14 January 1931 - 14 December 1932. (Box 33, Folder 11)
- Minutes - Missionary Auxiliary, 11 January 1933 - 18 December 1935. (Box 34, Folder 1)
- Minutes - Missionary Auxiliary, 15 January 1936 - 13 December 1938. (Box 34, Folder 2)
- Minutes - Missionary Auxiliary, 10 January 1939 - 13 August 1940. (Box 34, Folder 3)
- Minutes - Missionary Auxiliary Executive Meetings, 15 September 1931 - 8 January 1940. (Box 34, Folder 4)
- Minutes - Official Board, 16 January 1922 - 28 September 1925. (Box 34, Folder 5)
- Minutes - Official Board, 17 November 1952 - 7 June 1954. (Box 34, Folder 6)
- Minutes - Official Board, 12 July 1954 - 1 June 1959. (Box 34, Folder 7)
- Minutes - Official Board, 12 July 1954 - 1 June 1959. (Box 35, Folder 1-2)
- Minutes - Official Board, July 1959 - 8 March 1965. (Box 35, Folder 3-5)
- Minutes - Richmond District Board of Church Location and Building, 9 June 1977 - 16 March 1985. (Box 35, Folder 6)
- Minutes - Sallie Lewis Brown Circle, 3 February 1977 - 14 February 1980. (Box 35, Folder 7)
- Minutes - Sallie Lewis Brown Circle, January 1980 - December 1988. (Box 35, Folder 8)
- Minutes - Sallie Lewis Brown Circle, February 1980 - October 1983. (Box 35, Folder 9)
- Minutes - Sallie Lewis Brown Circle, November 1983 - 7 January 1988. (Box 36, Folder 1)
- Minutes - Sallie Lewis Brown Circle, 7 January 1988 - 4 January 1990. (Box 36, Folder 2)
- Minutes - Sallie Lewis Brown Circle, 4 January 1990 - 5 May 1993. (Box 36, Folder 3)
- Minutes - Sallie Lewis Brown Circle, 2 September 1993 - 2 January 1997. (Box 36, Folder 4)
- Minutes - United Methodist Women, 8 January 1974 - 15 November 1977. (Box 36, Folder 5)
- Minutes - United Methodist Women, 17 January 1978 - 11 November 1980. (Box 36, Folder 6)
- Minutes - United Methodist Women, 8 September 1981 - 14 September 1982. (Box 36, Folder 7)
- Minutes - United Methodist Women, 9 November 1982 - 12 November 1985. (Box 36, Folder 8)
- Minutes - United Methodist Women, 11 March 1986 - 9 November 1988. (Box 36, Folder 9)
- Minutes - United Methodist Women, 13 March 1990 - 15 November 1994. (Box 36, Folder 10)
- Minutes - United Methodist Women, 10 January 1995 - 12 May 1998. (Box 36, Folder 11)
- Minutes - United Methodist Women Executive Committee, 1984-1986. (Box 36, Folder 12)
- Minutes - United Methodist Women Executive Committee, 1987-1998. (Box 36, Folder 13)
- Minutes - Wesleyan Bible Class, 6 October 1941 - 20 September 1948. (Box 36, Folder 14)
- Minutes - Woman's Society of Christian Service, 17 September 1940 - 28 June 1943. (Box 37, Folder 1)
- Minutes - Woman's Society of Christian Service, 9 November 1943 - 14 May 1946. (Box 37, Folder 2)
- Minutes - Woman's Society of Christian Service, 11 June 1946 - 11 March 1947. (Box 37, Folder 3)
- Minutes - Woman's Society of Christian Service, 10 February 1948 - 20 March 1952. (Box 37, Folder 4)
- Minutes - Woman's Society of Christian Service, June 1952 - May 1956. (Box 37, Folder 5-7)
- Minutes - Woman's Society of Christian Service, 10 May 1960 - 14 April 1964. (Box 37, Folder 8)
- Minutes - Woman's Society of Christian Service, 14 January 1969 - 13 November 1973. (Box 37, Folder 9)
- Miscellaneous. (Box 37, Folder 10)
- Mission Letters. (Box 37, Folder 11)
- Mother of the Year. (Box 37, Folder 12)
- Music - Psalm Settings. (Box 38, Folder 1)
- National Council of Churches. (Box 38, Folder 2)
- NationsBank. (Box 38, Folder 3)
- Newsletter Items. (Box 38, Folder 4)
- Nurturing Committee. (Box 38, Folder 5)
- Official Board, 1956-1959. (Box 38, Folder 6-9)
- Official Board, 1959-1960. (Box 38, Folder 10)
- Organist Director. (Box 38, Folder 11)
- Organist Resumes, 1998. (Box 38, Folder 12)
- "Our Story of the Church" by Berryman Juniors, June 1960. (Box 38, Folder 13)
- Parents Night Out, 1997-1998. (Box 38, Folder 14)
- Pastor-Parish Relations Committee. (Box 38, Folder 15)
- Patrick Henry School. (Box 38, Folder 16)
- Pettigrew, William H. - Estate. (Box 38, Folder 17)
- Photographs. (Box 39, Folder 1)
- Photographs - Oversize. (Box Oversize Box 65)
- Photograph (Rolled) - 155th Session, Baltimore Conference, Methodist Episcopal Church, South, Roanoke, Virginia, 2-4 October 1939. (Box 55)
- Photographs of Former Pastors. (Box 39, Folder 2-3)
- Pledge Cards. (Box 39, Folder 4)
- Prayer Guides. (Box 39, Folder 5)
- Program - "Where the Money Goes". (Box 39, Folder 6)
- Quarterly Conference Record Book, 1926-1930. (Box 39, Folder 7)
- Quarterly Conference Reports, 1944-1949. (Box 39, Folder 8)
- Quarterly Conference Reports, 1950-1954. (Box 39, Folder 9)
- Raney, Bill (File Cabinet). (Box 39, Folder 10)
- Receipts, 1963-1968. (Box 39, Folder 11-16)
- Receipts, 1969. (Box 40, Folder 1)
- Receipts, 1994. (Box 40, Folder 2-3)
- Receipts, 1997. (Box 40, Folder 4)
- Receipts and Disbursements, 1963-1971. (Box 55)
- Receipts and Disbursements, 2000. (Box 55)
- Receipts and Disbursements, 2001. (Box 55)
- Recording Steward, 1977-1978. (Box 40, Folder 5)
- Register of Charter Members. (Box 49)
- Register of Pastors, Baptisms, Marriages, amd Members, 1913-1960. (Box 56)
- Revealing Christ Campaign, 1988. (Box 40, Folder 6)
- Richmond District. (Box 40, Folder 7)
- Richmond Home for Ladies. (Box 40, Folder 8)
- "Richmond Living Memories" by James Mead. (Box 40, Folder 9)
- Richmond Music Teachers Association - Yearbook, 1990-1991. (Box 40, Folder 10)
- The Ritual, the General Rules, and Articles of Religion of the Methodist Episcopal Church, South, 1914. (Box 40, Folder 11)
- Sacrifice Box. (Box 40, Folder 12)
- "St. Andrew's Messenger," 1973-1977. (Box 40, Folder 13)
- Sands, Lily E. - Estate. (Box 40, Folder 14)
- Satterwhite Class. (Box 40, Folder 15)
- Satterwhite Class - Bank Book, 1958-1960. (Box 40, Folder 16)
- Satterwhite Class - Bank Statements, 1958-1959. (Box 40, Folder 17)
- Satterwhite Class - Constitution and By-Laws. (Box 40, Folder 18)
- Satterwhite Class - Record Books, 1941-1957. (Box 50)
- Satterwhite Class - Record Books, 1957-1959, 1968. (Box 51)
- Satterwhite Class - Treasurer's Book, 1946-1949. (Box 40, Folder 19)
- School Roll, n.d.. (Box 41, Folder 1)
- Scrapbook - Woman's Society of Christian Service. (Box 41, Folder 2)
- Season Lectionary Readings. (Box 41, Folder 3)
- Senior Citizen Resources. (Box 41, Folder 4)
- Senior Dept. - Treasurer's Book, 1948-1950. (Box 41, Folder 5)
- Serial Numbers. (Box 41, Folder 6)
- 75th Anniversary. (Box 41, Folder 7)
- 75th Anniversary Program Proofs. (Box 41, Folder 8)
- 79th Anniversary. (Box 41, Folder 9)
- Sexton. (Box 41, Folder 10)
- Sherbourne Avenue Methodist Church. (Box 41, Folder 11)
- "Small-Membership Church Leadership". (Box 41, Folder 12)
- Software. (Box 41, Folder 13)
- SPP Project (Supervised Professional Practice). (Box 41, Folder 14)
- Stations of the Cross. (Box 41, Folder 15)
- Steering Committee, 2001. (Box 41, Folder 16)
- Stewardship. (Box 42, Folder 1)
- Sunday School Attendance, 1914-1959. (Box 42, Folder 2)
- Sunday School Attendance Record Book, 1930-1931. (Box 48)
- Sunday School Attendance Record Book, 1932-1934. (Box 48)
- Sunday School Attendance Record Book, 1934. (Box 48)
- Sunday School Attendance Records, 1956-1959. (Box 42, Folder 3)
- Sunday School Attendance Records, 1960. (Box 42, Folder 4)
- Sunday School Attendance Records, 1961. (Box 42, Folder 5)
- Sunday School Attendance Records, 1962-1964. (Box 42, Folder 6)
- Sunday School Attendance Records, 1964-1965. (Box 42, Folder 7)
- Sunday School Attendance Records, 1965-1966. (Box 42, Folder 8)
- Sunday School Attendance Records, 1967-1968. (Box 42, Folder 9)
- Sunday School Children, 2000. (Box 42, Folder 10)
- Sunday School Reports, 1966-1967. (Box 42, Folder 11)
- Sunday School Scrapbook, 1983. (Box 55)
- Sunday School Treasurer's Account Book, 1915-1920. (Box 42, Folder 12)
- Sunday School Treasurer's Account Book, 1920-1931. (Box 48)
- Sunday School Treasurer's Account Book, 1931-1941. (Box 48)
- SunTrust. (Box 43, Folder 1)
- Treasurer's Book, June 1963 - May 1964. (Box 51)
- Treasurer's Book, June 1964 - May 1965. (Box 51)
- Treasurer's Book, June 1965 - May 1966. (Box 51)
- Treasurer's Book, June 1966 - May 1967. (Box 52)
- Treasurer's Book, June 1968 - May 1969. (Box 52)
- Treasurer's Book, June-December, 1969. (Box 52)
- Treasurer's Book, 1970. (Box 52)
- Treasurer's Book - Improvement Fund, October 1965 - September 1967. (Box 53)
- Treasurer's Book - Improvement Fund, October 1967 - September 1969. (Box 53)
- Treasurer's Book - Improvement Fund, October 1969 - September 1970. (Box 53)
- Treasurer's Correspondence, 1958-1968. (Box 43, Folder 2)
- Treasurer's Reports, 1939-1940. (Box 43, Folder 3)
- Treasurer's Reports, 1959-1960. (Box 43, Folder 4)
- Treasurer's Reports, 1971. (Box 43, Folder 5)
- Treasurer's Reports, 1972. (Box 43, Folder 6)
- Treasurer's Reports, 1974. (Box 43, Folder 7)
- Treasurer's Reports, 1975. (Box 43, Folder 8)
- Treasurer's Reports, 1976. (Box 43, Folder 9)
- Treasurer's Reports, 1979-1982. (Box 43, Folder 10)
- Trustees. (Box 43, Folder 11)
- United Methodist Women, 1979-1982. (Box 43, Folder 12)
- United Methodist Women - Account Ledger, 1972-1976. (Box 43, Folder 13)
- United Methodist Women - Account Ledger, 1977-1980. (Box 43, Folder 14)
- United Methodist Women - Account Ledger, 1981. (Box 43, Folder 15)
- United Methodist Women - Account Ledger, 1982-1984. (Box 43, Folder 16)
- United Methodist Women - Account Ledger, 1985-1986. (Box 44, Folder 1)
- United Methodist Women - Account Ledger, 1987-1988. (Box 44, Folder 2)
- United Methodist Women - Bank Statements, 1976-1991. (Box 44, Folder 3-5)
- United Methodist Women - Certificates. (Box 44, Folder 6)
- United Methodist Women - Check Register, 1974-1981. (Box 44, Folder 7)
- United Methodist Women - Check Register, 1982-1987. (Box 44, Folder 8)
- United Methodist Women - Check Register, 1987-1988. (Box 44, Folder 9)
- United Methodist Women - Check Register, 1989-1991. (Box 44, Folder 10)
- United Methodist Women - Donations, 1994-1998. (Box 45, Folder 1-2)
- United Methodist Women - Life Memberships. (Box 45, Folder 3)
- United Methodist Women - Lists of Officers. (Box 45, Folder 4)
- United Methodist Women - Savings Account, 1981-1982. (Box 45, Folder 5)
- United Methodist Women - Treasurer's Reports, 1973, 1976-1980. (Box 45, Folder 6)
- United Methodist Women - Treasurer's Reports, 1980-1983. (Box 45, Folder 7)
- United Methodist Women - Treasurer's Reports, 1984-1986. (Box 45, Folder 8)
- United Methodist Women - Treasurer's Reports, 1986-1988. (Box 45, Folder 9)
- United Methodist Women - Treasurer's Reports, 1988-1989. (Box 45, Folder 10)
- United Methodist Women - Treasurer's Reports, 1990-1994. (Box 45, Folder 11)
- United Methodist Women - Treasurer's Reports, 1995-1998. (Box 45, Folder 12)
- United Methodist Women - Yearbooks. (Box 45, Folder 13-14)
- Upper Room Class - Record Book, 1973-1974. (Box 46, Folder 1)
- Upper Room Class - Record Book, 1975-1978. (Box 46, Folder 2)
- Vacation Bible School, 2001. (Box 46, Folder 3)
- "Virginia Advocate," 1995-2002. (Box 46, Folder 4)
- Virginia Conference Treasurer's Reports. (Box 46, Folder 5)
- Virginia Methodist Children's Home - Contributions, 1969. (Box 46, Folder 6)
- Visitor's Register - 80th Birthday, 26 September 1993. (Box 46, Folder 7)
- "Vital Congregations" Course. (Box 46, Folder 8)
- Wachovia. (Box 46, Folder 9)
- Wedding File. (Box 46, Folder 10)
- Weekly Reports to General Secretary of Local Church School, 1938-1939. (Box 46, Folder 11)
- Westview on the James. (Box 46, Folder 12)
- Woman's Division of Christian Service - Annual Report, 1960. (Box 46, Folder 13)
- Woman's Missionary Council - Certificates, 1936, 1940. (Box 46, Folder 14)
- Woman's Missionary Society. (Box 46, Folder 15)
- Woman's Society of Christian Service - Record and Report Book, 1952-1953. (Box 46, Folder 16)
- Woman's Society of Christian Service - Record and Report Book, 1952-1956. (Box 47, Folder 1-2)
- Woman's Society of Christian Service - Record and Report Book, 1956-1960. (Box 47, Folder 3-6)
- Woman's Society of Christian Service - Record and Report Book, 1960-1964. (Box 47, Folder 7-10)
- Woman's Society of Christian Service - Yearbook, 1972-1973. (Box 47, Folder 11)
- Worship Celebration Midweek Services, 1997-1998. (Box 47, Folder 12)
- Yearbook, 1945-194. (Box 47, Folder 13)
- Young People's Dept. - Scrapbook (WWII), 1943-1945. (Box 55)